{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Answer these questions about music from the years 2000-2009. ",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Justin Timberlake",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who brought sexy back?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Chris Brown",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who was Rihanna's abusive boyfriend?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ring",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "If you liked it then you should have put a what on it?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Jennifer Lopez",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What famous singer still considered herself \"Jenny from the Block\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Kelly Clarkson",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who won the first season of \"American Idol\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Eminem",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What rapper was the best-selling artist of the 2000's?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Destiny's Child",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What girl group sang \"Bootylicious\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "50 Cent",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What rapper survived nine gunshot wounds?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Polaroid Picture",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Complete the \"Hey Ya!\" lyrics: Shake it like a ________ _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Auto-Tune",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What pitch-correcting program was famously used by T-Pain?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Michael Jackson",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who died in Los Angeles on June 25, 2009?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Keith Urban",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What Australian country singer did Nicole Kidman marry?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Soulja Boy",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What 17-year old rapper had a #1 hit with \"Crank That\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Kanye West",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who dropped out of college, but then had a late registration and eventually graduated?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Coldplay",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "The lead singer of this band was formerly married to Gwenyth Paltrow"
  }, {
    "answer": "Emo",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What three-letter musical genre was exemplefied by \"Jimmy Eats World\" and \"Fall Out Boy\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Tim McGraw",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What country singer was Taylor Swift's first hit named after?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Rob Thomas",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who was the lead singer of Matchbox Twenty?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Guns N' Roses",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What band finally released its album \"Chinese Democracy\" after 10 years in development?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Detroit",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What city did The White Stripes hail from?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Paper Planes",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Which M.I.A song featured samples from \"Straight To Hell\" by The Clash"
  }, {
    "answer": "Usher",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Which R&B singer had the most total number one singles"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sisq√≥",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who sang the Thong Song?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Katy Perry",
    "category": "2000's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who kissed a girl and enjoyed it?"
  }],
  "quizLength": 20,
  "title": "2000's Music Trivia",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/2000s-music-trivia"
}
